Finding Aid for Center for Conflict Resolution (University of Michigan) records, 1952-1972
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Research
  - Research Projects
    - Chronological
      - Irwin Katz and Howard Schuman, 1968-169 (Box 12)
      - Tuskegee Project, 1968 (Box 12)
      - Miscellaneous Proposals, 1968-1970 (Box 13)
      - Advanced Research Projects Agency, 1968-1969 (Box 13)
      - J. David Singer, 1969 (Box 13)
      - ARPA Proposal; International Data Archive and Analysis Center, 1969 (Box 13)
      - Joseph Ben-Dak, 1970 (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous Proposals, 1970 (Box 13)
      - Gaye Crouch, 1971 (Box 13)
      - Judith Birnbaum, 1971 (Box 13)
      - Frithjof Bergman, 1971 (Box 13)
      - Proposals, undated (Box 13)
    - Research Seminars
      - Arms Control Research Seminar, 1961-1962; 3 folders (Box 13)
      - Internal/External Conflict Seminar, 1969 (Box 13)
      - Research Development Seminar
        - 1960 (Box 13)
        - 1960-1961, 3 folders (Box 13)
        - 1960-1962 (Box 13)
        - 1962, 2 folders (Box 13)
- Topical
  The Topical series consists of a small amount of clippings, memoranda, and correspondence related to particular topics such as the New Left and Vietnam. It is organized alphabetically by topic.
  - Black Militancy and Student Activism, 1968 (Box 13)
  - National Peace Agency Proposal, 1960-1964 (Box 13)
  - New Left Material, circa 1968 (Box 13)
  - PROBE; Feminism; Gaye Crouch, 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Thu-Van / Le Thi Anh, 1966 (Box 13)
  - United Nations University Seminar, 1961 (Box 13)
  - Vietnam, 1964-1968; 2 folders (Box 13)